#### https://dalvi-moreshwar.vercel.app/

# MORESHWAR DALVI



SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

A software developer with more than 5.5 years' experience, I work as an IT professional.

I am open to working with alternative technologies. With confidence and friendliness, I am able to work both individually and in teams effectively. As a problem-solver and analytical thinker, I am adept at solving

I am excited to learn about the latest technologies in the market and I have already developed good knowledge on Web 3.0. I would like to learn more about them in the future.



moreshwardlv@gmail.com

+91 90-9673-2777



https://github.com/DalviMoreshwar



@MoreshwarDalvi



🂢 86, Galli No 3, Behind Jain Basti, Narasobawadi-416104, Kolhapur India 茞 https://www.linkedin.com/in/moreshwar-dalvi-a84257ba/



# **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor Of Computer Science and Engineering

**DKTE Society's** 

Textile and Engineering Institute, Ichalkaranji [Shivaji University], Kolhapur.

08/2011 - 06/2016

#### Higher Secondary Certification Examination

Balavantrao Zele High School, Jaysingpur Kolhapur Divisional Board, [Shivaji University] Kolhapur. 07/2009 - 06/2011

## SKILLS

React Js	Redux	Node Js	Next JS
Blockchain	Hardhat	Solidity	Ethers Js

# PERSONAL PROJECTS

### **CRYPTO TRANSFER - Decentralized Application** 06/2022

Built Web 3.0 blockchain application, using new technologies like, React Js, Tailwind CSS, Solidity, Ethers Js, Hardhat, Metamask Wallet.

- Connected to Blockchain
- Metamask wallet paring
- Writing solidity Code
- Interaction with Smart Contracts
- Sending Ethereum through the Blockchain network

Demo: https://crypto-transfer-psi.vercel.app

Code: https://github.com/DalviMoreshwar/crypto-transfer

#### CRYPTO CURRENCY DASHBOARD 07/2022

Crypto currency tracker app using React Js, Material UI, and Chart JS with responsive functionality.

- ✓ Context API to manage the state
- Coin Gecko API for backend

Demo: https://crypto-currency-dashboard-woad.vercel.app Code: https://github.com/DalviMoreshwar/crypto-currencydashboard

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### FRONT END DEVELOPER

Pune, Remote

Acclivis Technologies Pvt Ltd | 09/2020 - Present

Smart System Designer (SSD) is a tool used to search for Electronic IC part information and helps choose better electronic components for the design.

- Developed front-end screens for the application. Created some reusable components and functions.
- API integrations.
- Used **Redux Thunk** in the project for state management.

### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Pune

BiCS Infotech Pvt. Ltd. | 06/2019 - 09/2020

MMRI Genetics Research Data (Masonic Medical Research Institute). Web portal for researched genetic data which is differentiated between Admin & Researcher.

- Learned React JS, Redux, Axios, & Developed front-end screens for the application. Tables, Searching, Sorting, Pagination, & data export functionality were added.
- API integrations.
- Created an API using Node Js, and MySQL as backend.

#### HYBRID-MOBILE APP DEVELOPMEN

Pune

InfoWorld Consultancy | May 2018 - July 2019

- Worked on a mobile application for power builder applications using Node JS as web service using IIS on windows local server.
- Worked on a mobile application for sap b1 using ASP.NET MVC web service & Ionic Framework.

## FRONT END + BACKEND DEVELOPER

Sangli & Pune

Dot Web Solutions Pvt. Ltd. | Sept. 2017 -May 2018 ZoomYourTraffic Web Solution Dec. 2016 -Sept. 2017

- Worked on web applications as well as mobile applications using ionic framework. Also created admin projects using Angular and PHP server-side and MySQL as databases.
- ✓ User Interface Developer. Worked on HTML, CSS, and JavaScript web technologies
- Started learning Angular JS (front end framework) and lonic mobile application framework